你妈还好吗
How's your mom holding up?
她还行  但我们又失去个看护了
She's doing okay, but we just lost another nurse.
-这是第几个了  -第二个
- How many is that now? - Two,
我知道你在想什么
and I know what you're thinking--
她们是被她吃掉的
she's eating them.
她太难伺候  看护都不想伺候了
She's just so impossible, they keep quitting.
那现在是谁在照看她
So, who's watching her now?
一碗掺了几颗安眠药的巧克力豆
A bowl full of M & M's with a few Ambien tossed in.
大家好啊
What up, guys?
-你来啦  -你好啊
- Hello. - Hey. Hello.
好的
Okay.
现在大家都到场了
Well, now that everyone's here,
我跟佩妮有件大事要宣布
Penny and I have some big news.
我们订婚了
We're engaged!
天啊
Oh my God!
我还以为我跟艾米丽上床了会是最大新闻呢
And I thought me having sex with Emily was gonna be the big news.
不带你们这样的
What the hell!
你们整天求婚来求婚去
You guys propose all the time.
而这是千年头一遭
This never happens.
你说得对
You're right!
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：纵横天下二十五载赛太公  陪伴人生无数春秋YY猫
太公生快有缘再见猫中王  恭贺寿星秋季再聚醉芝士
天啊  我今天超饿
Boy, I'm so hungry today.
你们说是为什么呢
I wonder why?
因为做爱消耗太多体力吗
Because you had sex the other night?
其实呢
You know what?
可能真是这原因哦
That may be it.
对了  这事没骑车这么简单
By the way, it isn't like riding a bike.
我摔了好几次呢
Like, I fell off a few times.
兄弟
Hey, buddy.
你好
Hello.
你没事吧
You okay?
我刚被叫进塞伯特校长的办公室
I just got called into President Siebert's office.
学校不准我
The university won't let me
把研究方向改为宇宙暴胀论
switch my field of study to inflationary cosmology.
他们逼我继续研究弦理论
They're forcing me to continue with string theory.
为什么
Why?
他说大学雇我是让我研究弦理论
He said it's why they hired me,
我的研究经费也仅限于研究弦理论
it's-it's what my grant was designated for,
而且每个人都有人在江湖身不由己的时候
and that everybody has to do things they don't want to do.
他还举了一个他身不由己的例子
He then gave an example of something he had to do,
就是虽然他十分不想
even though he didn't want to,
却还是不得不见我这傻逼
which was look at my stupid face.
他怎么能把这话
That's a rude thing to say.
说出口呢
Out loud.
这太过分了
It's an outrage.
老实说  我现在很想辞职走人
Honestly, I'm tempted to leave the university.
如果你是认真在考虑这事
You know, if you're really serious about that,
我听说在肥胖老人家庭看护领域
I hear there are some exciting opportunities
有些很不错的机会哦
in home care for the old and fat.
无论你想做什么  千万不要贸然行事
Whatever you do, just don't make any rash decisions.
我不知道
I don't know.
我现在超级不爽
I am really aggravated.
我心情低落的时候  我就跟妹子上床
When I'm feeling low, I have sex with a girl.
但这纯属个人喜好啦
But that's just me.
-别走嘛  再给她次机会  -不要
- Oh, come on, give her a chance. - No.
人生苦短  我得及时行乐
Life, it is too short.
我知道你才来做了一天半
I know you've only been here a day and a half,
但你就像我们的家人一样呢
but you're like part of the family!
我觉得看护中介不会再介绍人来了
I don't think the service is gonna send any more people.
看来我们只能把妈放回大海里了[鲸鱼]
Yeah, maybe it's time we just release Ma back into the sea.
开玩笑有什么用
That's not helpful.
那我们只能学着接受
Well, then, we may need to get used to the idea
接下来几个月得在这住的事实了
that we're gonna be living here the next few months.
但我们都有工作
But we have jobs.
哪有空一天到晚在这照顾她
We can't baby-sit her 24 hours a day.
我们把年假休掉啊
Well, what if we use our vacation time?
我的假期想留给夏威夷  不是地狱
I wanted to go to Hawaii, not Hell.
那我真是没招了
I don't know what else we can do.
华仔  我爱你
Howie, I love you,
作为你的妻子  你妈妈的问题
and as your wife, your mother is every bit
我责无旁贷  所以...
as much my problem as she is yours, so...
我想离婚
I want a divorce.
你好吗  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard.
你好啊  老妈
Hi, Mom.
我有件好消息要宣布
I have some exciting news.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
在我说之前
Before I tell you,
你能答应会尽量为我开心
will you promise to try and be happy for me
并把心中的疑虑都留在心里就好吗
and keep any concerns you have to yourself?
不行
No.
我就替你省了这支支吾吾的功夫吧
Let me save you all of your hemming and hawing.
谢尔顿告诉我你跟佩妮订婚了
Sheldon already told me that you and Penny are engaged.
我不喜欢你跟他聊比跟我聊还多
I-I hate that you talk to him more than you talk to me.
那你想我跟你多聊天吗
Would you like for you and me to talk more?
其实也还好啦
You know what? It's probably fine.
无论如何  虽然我曾有过疑虑
In any event, while I've had my misgivings about...
对佩妮这货
Penny...
但谢尔顿说了很多她的好话
...Sheldon spoke very fondly of her,
所以如果谢尔顿觉得她够好
and if she is good enough for him,
那我也会觉得她够好
then she's good enough for me.
我是你儿子呢
I'm your son.
那我觉得她够好就不算数吗
What about the fact that she's good enough for me?
算吧
Sure.
谢谢你啊  老妈
Thanks, Mom.
莱纳德  你听到你母亲赞同你的
Leonard, would it make you feel better to hear that
人生选择  你会比较开心吗
your mother approved of your life choices?
当然会
Yes, it would.
这是病  得治
Yeah. Well, you should work on that.
不是啦  妈
No, Mom, it's the same guy
就是我这两年一直在一起的那个男的
I've been going out with for the past two years.
对  就是那个科学家
Yeah, the scientist.
很复杂啦
Well, it's complicated.
他是鼓捣激光跟原子磁铁之类的
I mean, he works with lasers and atomic magnets.
没  我自己也没想到
No, I did not see it coming.
没  我们也没订日子
No, we did not set a date.
没  我没怀孕
No, I am not pregnant.
是啊  这是咱家头一遭呢
Yeah, this is a first for our family.
好啦  告诉老爸我爱他  我要挂了
All right, tell Dad I love him. I gotta go.
好  再见
All right, bye.
-原子磁铁吗  -闭嘴
- Atomic magnets? - Shut up.
抱歉迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
吹叶机坏了
The leaf blower broke,
我只能手动擦干我婆婆
so I had to hand-dry my mother-in-law.
要来一杯吗
You want some wine?
好的
Thanks.
在你跳进婚姻这个大坑前  姐先嘱咐你两句
Little warning before you jump into this marriage business:
你嫁的不光是他这个人
You're not just marrying him,
还有他的家庭
you're marrying his family.
我觉得莱纳德的妈妈对我没意见
I think Leonard's mom's okay with me.
有没有意见倒是无所谓
It doesn't matter if she's okay with you.
重点是  她能不能自己上厕所
The question is: Can she go to the bathroom by herself?
再来一杯
Hit me again.
那你们打算在哪儿住
So, what are the living arrangements gonna be?
我们还没谈到这个问题
Well, haven't really talked about it yet,
但我猜到最后
but I figure, at some point,
不是我搬去跟他住  就是他搬来跟我住
I'll move in with him, or he'll move in with me.
你现在没工作  住在一起的确比较省钱
Well, with you not working, that makes financial sense.
你现在没工作
You're not working!
你有没有兴趣做家庭看护啊
How would you like a job in home health care?
门儿都没有
Not a chance.
-拜托了  我都要绝望了  -不要
- Please. I'm desperate. - No.
-薪水你说了算  -那好吧
- I'll pay you anything you want. - Okay, then, yeah.
我不干了  钱你留着请别人吧
No! Keep your money!
老娘骑电动牛的时间都比这个长
I could've ridden a bull longer than that.
酒吧里仿牛仔驯牛的游戏机器
人们骑上去挑战不被摔下来  持续时间久可赢得奖品
你在忙什么呢
What you working on?
我向教授评议会提出上诉
I'm writing an appeal to the Faculty Senate,
要求不再研究弦理论  转而研究其他方向
so that I can move on from string theory.
写得怎么样了
Oh. How's it going?
给点意见呗
You tell me.
"各位尊敬的同事们
"Dear Esteemed Colleagues,
或许你们有所耳闻  我要求更改我的研究领域
as you may know, I have requested to change my field of study.
我之所以作此决定  是因为我相信
My decision to do so is, I believe,
这样做对科学界是最好的
in the best interest of science.
如你们有时间  我非常乐意用你们听得懂的词语
At your convenience, I'd be happy to explain it to you
好好解释一番"
in words you'll understand."
你在称呼前加个"尊敬的"  还算有礼貌
It's nice that you called them "Esteemed."
你说得对  我应该删掉它
You're right. I'll take that out.
对了  有件事我想跟你说一下
So, listen, there was something I was hoping to float past you.
因为我和佩妮订婚了
Now that Penny and I are engaged,
我想我们可能需要讨论一下住的问题
I thought we might want to talk about our living arrangements.
当然
Of course.
她总是在这里过夜
She's spent many nights here,
所以你担心在婚礼之前
and you're worried about preserving
没办法对她的童贞问题进行保密吗
the myth of her virginity before the wedding.
不是啦
I'm not.
那就好  因为她的童贞船早已远航
Good, because not only has that ship sailed,
而且如果撞到冰山  肯定会死一大片男人
if it hit an iceberg, countless men would perish.
其实我想跟你讨论的是  我和她的住宿问题
Actually, this is about where she and I are going to live.
什么意思
What do you mean?
那个...我们俩可能想住在一起
Well... well, we might want to live together.
是吗  我早就考虑过这个问题了
Oh, yeah, well, I've already given this some thought,
我呢
and...
也很乐意让佩妮跟我们一起住
I'm willing to let Penny live with us
考察期时每周可以住一天哦
one day a week for a trial period.
当然她子宫内膜脱落
Now, obviously, not when she's made cranky
脾气暴躁的那几天不能来这住
by the shedding of her uterine lining.
你考虑得真周全
That's very sweet.
但我们更多考虑的是  我们俩住在一起
But we were thinking more of us maybe living together with...
没你
not you.
我不懂
I don't understand.
如果没我  我们怎么能都住在一起呢
How could we all live together if I'm not there?
听着  我知道这是一种改变
Look, I-I know this is... this is change,
听起来很可怕  但是
and that sounds scary, but...
那你要去哪里住
Where are you going to go?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们才开始考虑这个问题
We just started to think about this.
或许我会搬去跟佩妮住
Maybe I'll move in with Penny,
又或许她会搬进来跟我住
or maybe she and I'll take this place,
而你搬到对面住
and you can move across the hall.
搬到对面住
Move across the hall?!
你抽大麻了吗
Did you take a marijuana?!
没有
No, I did not.
那你是脑子被椰子砸了吗
Did you get hit on the head with a coconut?
-也没有  -那我想不到原因了
- No. - Well, then, I'm all out of guesses.
你居然让我搬到对面住
What? Me move across the hall--
这种话你怎么好意思说出口
Why would you even suggest such a thing?
因为我爱佩妮
Because I love Penny,
我想给她她应得的生活
and want to give her the life she deserves.
我明白了
I see.
看来你未来老婆的幸福生活远比我的重要
You're putting your future bride's happiness above mine.
没错
Well, yeah.
学校居然敢强迫我继续研究弦理论
How dare the university force me to go back to string theory!
那是他们不懂得欣赏你
They just don't appreciate you.
对啊  最过分的是
Yeah, and on top of that,
莱纳德居然厚颜无耻地提出
Leonard has the audacity to suggest that
因为他跟佩妮订婚了
now that he and Penny are engaged,
他可能不想再跟我一起住了
he may not want to live with me anymore.
给  我做了草莓热饮
Here, I made you some Strawberry Quik.
我现在有正经问题要处理  艾米
I have real problems here, Amy.
小孩喝的饮料怎么能平息我的怒火呢
I can't be mollified with a beverage designed for children.
哇  真好喝
Mmm! Yummy.
一切都会变好的
You know, this might work out for the best.
我是说  你总是抱怨
I mean, you're always complaining about
莱纳德是一位很糟糕的室友
what a terrible roommate Leonard is.
像上次你不在  他擅自打开了恒温器
Like how he turns up the thermostat when you're not there.
打开门就像走进了亚马逊
It's like walking into the Amazon.
而且还不是可以一日送货的亚马逊网站
And not the good Amazon with one-day shipping.
而是鸟多蛇多的亚马逊丛林
The awful one with birds and snakes.
你讨厌听到他钥匙扣上的碰撞声
You hate the sound of all those keys on his key chain.
整整四把钥匙
Four keys!
他以为他是谁  典狱长吗
Who does he think he is, a warden?
瞧  或许你会喜欢独居
See? Maybe you'll love living alone.
我不知道  或许吧
I don't know. Perhaps.
如果你发现自己不喜欢的话
And if it turns out you don't...
你可以跟我一起住啊
you and I could live together.
跟你住  是啊
You and... Oh, sure.
既然我们谈到这话题了  何不索性订个婚
And while we're at it, why don't we get engaged, too?
再买个房子  成个家
Why don't we get a little house, start a family?
然后一起慢慢变老
Enjoy our sunset years together?
拜托自重一点好吗  姑娘
Do you hear yourself, woman?!
谢尔顿  这只是一个想法而已
Sheldon, it was just a thought.
不  这才叫想法
No. Here's a thought.
你不准搬过来
You're not moving in,
莱纳德不准搬出去
Leonard's not moving out,
一切保持原状  不准改变
everything stays exactly the way it is.
对了  随便一提
Yeah, and by the way,
我看到你冲草莓热饮时偷加糖浆了
I saw you make this Strawberry Quik with syrup,
按规矩应该是加糖粉的
and you're supposed to use the powder!
喝起来不都一样吗
It tastes the same.
才怪  糖浆口感更好  人家不喜欢
No. The syrup tastes better and I don't like it.
太有爱了
This is so sweet!
-你从没给我做过饭  -那是因为
- You never cook for me. - Well...
以前都是你做饭  而且...
you cook for me all the time and...
你要是不喜欢我做的饭
If you don't like my cooking,
干嘛不早说
why haven't you ever said anything?
每次都得猛嚼食物   哪里有空说话
It's hard to talk with so much heavy chewing to do.
对不起  我会努力改进的
Sorry. I'll get better.
我知道你会的
I know you'll try.
我们是不是该讨论一下婚礼的日子呢
So, should we talk about setting a date?
我想挑一个我哥能参加的日子
Well, I'd like to pick one that works with my brother's schedule.
好啊  大概是什么时候
Okay. And when would that be?
如果他表现良好  一年或一年半以后吧
Uh, 12 to 18 months from now, depending on good behavior.
谢尔顿在吗
Hi, is Sheldon here?
不在  我以为他跟你在一起呢
No, I thought he was with you.
他来过  可又摔门而去
He was, but he stormed off
现在他连电话都不接了
and now he isn't answering his phone.
出什么事了
What happened?
他为了你让他搬家的事大发雷霆
He was really angry that you suggested he move out.
我建议他可以搬来和我同住
I also mentioned that he and I could live together
可他太生你的气了
but he was too mad at you to realize
都没注意到这个主意有多棒
what a great idea that is.
这几天他的确不太好过
Well, he's been having a couple of tough days.
他会没事的  他只是需要
I'm sure he's fine. He probably just
一点时间来缓解压力
needs a little alone time to decompress.
你说得对
You're probably right.
你们俩在干嘛呢
So, what are you guys doing?
莱纳德下了厨  我们作为
Well, Leonard cooked for me and now we're just having
新晋订婚的爱侣  正在享用美好的晚餐
a nice dinner, you know, as a newly engaged couple.
真幸福
That's nice.
总之  就像我之前所说
Anyway, as I was saying,
谢尔顿大概只是需要独处一下
Sheldon probably just needs a little alone time.
独处是很重要的
'Cause that's important.
不光对他而言  而是对
Not just for him, but for...
大部分人而言  都很重要
most anybody, really.
我也有同感呢
Don't I know it.
这是什么  玉米粥吗
What is that, polenta?
-艾米  快滚蛋  -好吧
- Amy, get out. - Right.
不会吧
No.
嗨  谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon.
出什么事了
What happened?
昨晚我在后面做饭
I was cooking in the back room last night
结果锅子起火了
and the hot plate caught on fire.
你没把火扑灭吗
And you couldn't put it out?
我当时正在街对面的
I was across the street
自助洗车行里洗澡呢
at the do-it-yourself car wash, taking a shower.
那你准备何时重新开张
So when will you reopen?
我不知道
Um, I don't know.
我还在等保险公司的答复
I'm waiting to hear back from the insurance company.
就是明天吗
So, tomorrow?
我不想太没礼貌  谢尔顿  可是
I don't mean to be rude, Sheldon, but, uh,
我的人生都快分崩离析了
my life is kind of falling apart right now.
你的人生
Your life?
大学逼着我继续研究弦理论
The university is making me do string theory
我的女友爱我爱得想和我同居
and my girlfriend loves me so much she wants to live with me.
现在唯一能抚平我悲伤的小店
And now, the place I need to go when I'm sad
又湿又烂  还一股怪味
is damp and smells funny.
抱歉让你失望了
Well, sorry I let you down.
不
No.
我不能接受这种事
I do not accept this.
所有的一切都变了  我不喜欢这样
Everything is changing and I hate it.
我要阻止这种改变
It stops now.
我要帮你重新振作起来
I'm helping you get back on your feet.
我要买这本漫画  谢谢
I would like to purchase this comic book, please.
2块9毛9
That'll be $2.99.
不会吧  这书都泡湿了呢
Really? It's soaking wet.
好吧  算你1块钱
Fine, a dollar.
你找的开20元吗
Can you break a 20?
不能  我只剩下百元大钞了
No, I only have hundreds.
你知道吗
You know what?
我一般都听不出讽刺  但我现在听懂了
I don't always recognize sarcasm, but I do right now,
人家一点都不喜欢
and I don't appreciate it.
对你的损失  我感到惋惜
I'm sorry for your loss.
但你不是唯一遭受重创的人
But you're not the only one whose day has been a disaster.
这玩意差点就能砸死我呢
That could have killed me.
还让不让人活了啊
I can't catch a break.
好久都没有谢尔顿的消息了
I haven't heard from Sheldon in a while.
他应该没事吧
You think he's okay?
我保证他没事啦
Oh, I'm sure he's fine.
我看看他人在哪里
I'm gonna see where he is.
怎么看
How?
我知道他的密码  所以可以追踪他的手机
Oh, I know his password, so I can track his phone.
你居然做这种事
You do that?
不是经常做
Not always,
但自从他在跳蚤市场追着气球跑迷路以后
but ever since he wandered off at the swap meet chasing a balloon,
我就多留一个心眼
I get worried.
他会照顾好自己的
He can take care of himself.
我们教过他陌生人有多危险
Look, we went over stranger danger
也给他买了一只应急口哨
and gave him that whistle.
-真奇怪  -怎么了
- That's weird. - What?
他人在火车站呢
He's at the train station.
那又怎样  他最爱火车了
So? He loves trains.
外面天黑了  他又独自一人  我感觉不对
It's dark out and he's alone, I don't like it.
我们去找他吧
Let's go get him.
你这么照顾朋友  真是贴心
Oh, it's sweet how you look out for him.
你是个善良的人
You're a good guy.
也不光是善良
It's not just that.
如果他出了事  我妈铁定不会放过我
My mother would kill me if I let something happen to him.
老弟  我很抱歉
Dude, I'm so sorry.
你别介意我这么问
Don't take this the wrong way,
不过你是为了骗保险费吗
but did you do this for the insurance money?
才不是  天啊  你怎么和警察  消防员
No. God, you sound like the police, the firemen,
我爹妈  我心理医生还有保险公司想得一样
my parents, my therapist and the insurance company.
我们支持你  有任何需要就说话
We're here for you, man. Whatever you need, okay?
其实呢  我在想能不能
Uh, actually, I was wondering if I could
在你家借宿几晚
crash at your place for a few nights.
当然可以
Sure, of course.
不过  艾米丽今晚要来过夜呢
Oh, actually, Emily was gonna spend the night.
你和她睡过了吗  行啊
You slept with her? Nice.
不能说我有多能耐啦
Well, I can't take all the credit.
是她准我才上的  但是
She let me do it to her, but...
但我可以打电话跟她取消约会
Uh, but I can always call her and cancel.
慢着  我知道有个地方你可以住
Hang on. I know a place you can stay
而且还可以赚点钱
and earn some money at the same time.
-太好了  -只是我要警告你
- Great. - I just have to warn you,
这其中会涉及侮辱  没人格以及言语虐待
it'll involve humiliation, degradation and verbal abuse.
这工作的陷阱在哪呢
So what's the catch?
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
你追踪了我的电话
You tracked my phone?
是的
Yeah.
天啊  你追了我这颗气球整整3英里啊
Boy, you chase one balloon for three miles.
我们担心你
We were worried about you.
别这么夸张
Don't be melodramatic.
我只是准备登上火车  永远离开
I'm just getting on a train and leaving forever.
你不是吧
Seriously?
你甚至没带换洗衣物和牙刷
You don't even have a change of clothes or a toothbrush.
我的计划是路过商场时买必需物品
My plan is to stop at malls and buy what I need.
这叫靠山吃山  靠水吃水
It's called living off the land.
我知道你不高兴
Okay, I know you're upset
发生了太多事
and there's a lot of stuff going on,
但一切都好商量
but it's nothing we can't work out.
来吧  咱们回家
Come on, let's get you home.
不  我已经到达了人生的奔溃点了
No. I've reached my breaking point.
我需要离开  现在就走
I need to leave. Now.
去哪里
And go where?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
生活中有几件事不如你意
So a few things don't go your way
你就决定像个流浪汉般坐火车远走高飞吗
and your best decision is to ride the rails like a hobo?
我想是的
I suppose it is.
只是我有信用卡
Except I have a credit card.
我拒绝用扁担挑着笔记本走
And I refuse to carry my laptop at the end of a stick.
而且我宁死也不愿吃罐头豆子
And I'd sooner die than eat beans out of a can.
拜托  和我们回家吧
Come on, come home with us
明天我带你去乐高乐园
and tomorrow I'll-I'll take you to Legoland.
乐高乐园不是一切问题的解决办法
Legoland is not the solution to everything.
而且《乐高大电影》问世后
And it's too much of a scene
那里就人满为患了
since that movie came out.
那我能做些什么
Then what can I do?
莱纳德  我不知所措
Leonard, I am overwhelmed.
一切都在改变  多到让人无法接受
Everything is changing and it's simply too much.
我需要离开  好好想想
I need to get away and think.
拜托  你知道你自己是反应过度了
Oh, c-come on, you know you're overreacting.
莱纳德  等等
Leonard, hang on.
过来一下
Just... come here for a second.
也许我们需要让他走
Maybe we need to let him go.
什么  为什么呀
What?! Why?
也许对他有好处
It might be good for him.
你知道他没办法这样一个人旅行
Y-You know he can't take a trip like this by himself.
他是个成年人
He's a grown man.
不  他外表是成年人
No, he looks like a grown man.
你也看过《辣妈辣妹》
You've seen Freaky Friday,
有时候小孩子的灵魂会换到大人的身体里
sometimes little kids end up in big person bodies.
莱纳德  我们不能永远保护他
Leonard, we can't protect him forever.
我知道  但是
I know, but...
他不会有事的
He'll be okay.
你把他教得很好  巴达旺[绝地学徒]
You taught him well, Padawan.
老天爷
Good Lord!
巴达旺是学生  不是老师
Padawan's the student, not the teacher.
真的  让他滚
Seriously, let him go.
谢尔顿  如果你真的想这样
Sheldon, if you really need to do this,
我不会拦着你
I'm not gonna stand in your way.
我想
I do.
好吧
Okay.
一路顺风
Good luck.
注意安全  打电话给我们
Be safe and call us.
我会的
I will.
再见  兄弟
Bye, buddy.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
什么事
Yes?
我会想你的
I'm gonna miss you.
这不废话吗
Of course you are.
慢走不送
He just made that easier.
你们怎么还在这里
What are you guys still doing here?
我能搞定  快回家吧
I got this, go. Go home.
你确定吗
You sure?
她吃过饭  吃过药
Yeah, she's fed, she took her pills,
已经盖好被子看电视了
she's all tucked in and watching TV.
你没觉得她难伺候吗
So, she's not too much for you?
开什么玩笑  我爱她  她太棒了
Are you kidding? I love her, she's great.
小图图  你要和我一起看《幸运之轮》吗
Stewie, you gonna watch Wheel of Fortune with me?
来啦  黛比
Coming, Debbie.
你叫她黛比吗
You call her Debbie?
她坚持这样叫
She insisted.
两位  太感谢了
So, hey, guys, thank you so much.
这份工作真是美梦成真
This job is a dream come true.
这是不是有些奇怪
Was that a little weird?
是的  我不知道原因
Yeah. I don't know why,
但这事有些地方让人觉得
but something about it feels...
逆天了
unnatural.
-好啦  咱们走人  -好滴
- Okay, let's go. - Yep.
谢尔顿  多谢打电话来
Okay, Sheldon, thanks for checking in.
明天再通电话好吗
Talk to you tomorrow?
好的  拜
O-Okay, bye.
他还好吗
He's okay?
居然听起来非常好
Actually sounds like he's doing pretty well.
我真心觉得这样最好
I really think this is gonna be for the best.
我也是
Me, too.
这样他可以休下大学给的假期
And he was able to take a sabbatical from...
你这个天杀的怎么能放他走呢
How could you let him go?